const players = [
  {
    name: "Player 1",
    id: 0,
  },
  {
    name: "Player 2",
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    name: "Player 3",
    id: 2,
  },
];

const categories0 = [
  {
    title: "Why, Why, Y",
  },
  {
    title: "Before & After",
  },
  {
    title: "Jason Lore",
  },
  {
    title: "12 Days",
  },
  {
    title: "General Knowledge",
  },
]
const categories = [
  {
    title: "League of Legends",
  },
  {
    title: "Before & After",
  },
  {
    title: "Secret Technique",
  },
  {
    title: "O for Owendell",
  },
  {
    title: "General Knowledge",
  },
]

const questions0 = [
  {
    question: "Japanese Mafia",
    answer: "Yakuza",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Christmas Period Observed by Modern-Day Pagans",
    answer: "Yuletide",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Pint-Sized Race From Video Game Series League of Legends",
    answer: "Yordle",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Atomic Number 39",
    answer: "Yttrium",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The Norse Tree of Life",
    answer: "Yggsdrasil",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "Headlined Coachella 2023 by Causing a Fecal Related Occular Infection",
    answer: "Blackpink Eye",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 6,
  },
  {
    question: "Stolen by Benjamin Franklin Gates in a 1996 Film Starring Will Smith",
    answer: "Declaration of Independence Day",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "Refrain From Touching Yourself This Month While Wearing the Poppy",
    answer: "No Nut November 11th",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 8,
  },
  {
    question: "Dystopian Novel by George Orwell Could Not be Found Due to an Error Code",
    answer: "198404",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 9,
  },
  {
    question: "Mattress Supporting Structure Used to Determine How Something is Approached or Perceived",
    answer: "Bed Frame of Reference",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "This is My Korean Full Name",
    answer: "Chiyoung Jang",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 11,
  },
  {
    question: "This was My Dorm Number in RVC",
    answer: "1111",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "This is the Town Where I Did High School",
    answer: "Fort Nelson",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question: "This is the One Liquor I Won't Drink",
    answer: "Midori",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question: "This Common Type of Cake I will not Consume",
    answer: "Black Forest Cake",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "Fifth Day",
    answer: "Golden Rings",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 16,
  },
  {
    question: "Second Day",
    answer: "Turtle Doves",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 17,
  },
  {
    question: "Fourth Day",
    answer: "Calling Birds",
    points: 300,
    double: true,
    id: 18,
  },
  {
    question: "Twelfth Day",
    answer: "Drummers Drumming",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 19,
  },
  {
    question: "Ninth Day",
    answer: "Ladies Dancing",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 20,
  },
  {
    question: "This Actor Played Wolverine",
    answer: "Hugh Jackman",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 21,
  },
  {
    question: "This Email Service is Owned by Microsoft",
    answer: "Hotmail",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 22,
  },
  {
    question: "This Planet Has the Most Gravity in Our Solar System",
    answer: "Jupiter",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 23,
  },
  {
    question: "South Park's First Episode Aired on this Year",
    answer: "1997",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 24,
  },
  {
    question: "This Dutch Makeup Artist Came Out as Transgender in 2020",
    answer: "De Jager",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 25,
  },
]

const questions1 = [
  {
    question: "I First Spawn at 20 Minutes and Respawn Every 7 Minutes After I've Been Slain",
    answer: "Baron Nashor",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Found on the Edge of the Top Lane and Bottom Lane; Often Where Homies Would Go To Kiss (haha jk...unless?)",
    answer: "Alcove",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Janna: W",
    answer: "Zephyr",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "This Is Miss Fortune's Real Name",
    answer: "Sarah Fortune",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The Alpaca Boy Who Won Worlds 2022",
    answer: "Deft",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "2023 Biographical Thriller Film Starring A Yordel Scientist",
    answer: "Oppenheimerdinger",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 6,
  },
  {
    question: "DC Team of Superheroes Try to Take Down the Enemy Nexus in a MOBA Game",
    answer: "Justice League of Legends",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "Filipino Poultry Dish is the Star of Netflix's Inside",
    answer: "Chicken AdoBo Burnham",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 8,
  },
  {
    question: "Iconic Star Wars OST is a North American Collegiate Basketball Tournament",
    answer: "The Imperial March Madness",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 9,
  },
  {
    question: "Point of Elation You May Feel During a Marathon That is Mainly Used in Processed Foods, Cereals, Baked Goods, and Some Beverages",
    answer: "Runner's High Fructose Corn Syrup",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "Kamehameha",
    answer: "Dragonball",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 11,
  },
  {
    question: "Thunderbolt",
    answer: "Pokemon",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "Rasengan",
    answer: "Naruto",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question: "Gomu Gomu No Pistol",
    answer: "One Piece",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question: "Getsuga No Tenshou",
    answer: "Bleach",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "Annual Film Reward Show",
    answer: "Oscars",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 16,
  },
  {
    question: "The Transfer of Water Through A Permeable Membrane",
    answer: "Osmosis",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 17,
  },
  {
    question: "Bang, Bam, Bop, Bada-bop-boom, Pow ",
    answer: "Onomatopeia",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 18,
  },
  {
    question: "Mommy? Sorry. Mommy? Sorry.",
    answer: "Oedipus Complex",
    points: 400,
    double: true,
    id: 19,
  },
  {
    question: "A Significant Uptick in Membership Came in April 2020 When Beyonce Name-Dropped This Platform",
    answer: "OnlyFans",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 20,
  },
  {
    question: "The United States Bought Alaska From This Country",
    answer: "Russia",
    points: 100,
    double: false,
    id: 21,
  },
  {
    question: "This is the Hottest Planet in our Solar System",
    answer: "Venus",
    points: 200,
    double: false,
    id: 22,
  },
  {
    question: "This Actress Won the Oscar for Best Actress in 2003",
    answer: "Nicole Kidman",
    points: 300,
    double: false,
    id: 23,
  },
  {
    question: "This Fandom Stans the Korean K-Pop Group 2NE1",
    answer: "Blackjacks",
    points: 400,
    double: false,
    id: 24,
  },
  {
    question: "Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A and Start",
    answer: "Konami Code",
    points: 500,
    double: false,
    id: 25,
  },
]


export { players, categories, questions1 };
